export const quiz5 = {
    topic: 'Bipolar',
    totalQuestions: 10,
    questions: [
        {
            question: "You felt so good or hyper that other people thought you were not your normal self or were so hyper that you got into trouble?",
            answers: ["Yes", "No"]
          },
          {
            question: "At times I am MUCH more talkative or speak MUCH faster than usual.",
            answers: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question: "You were so irritable that you shouted at people or started fights or arguments?",
            answers: ["Yes", "No"]
          },
          {
            question: "There have been times when I was MUCH more active or did MANY more things than usual. ",
            answers: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question: "You felt much more self-confident than usual?",
            answers: ["Yes", "No"]
          },
          {
            question: "I get into moods where I feel VERY speeded up or irritable.",
            answers: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question: "You got much less sleep than usual and found you didn’t really miss it?",
            answers: ["Yes", "No"]
          },
          {
            question: "There have been times when I have felt both high (elated) and low (depressed) AT THE SAME TIME. ",
            answers: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          },
          {
            question: "Thoughts raced through your head or you couldn’t slow your mind down?",
            answers: ["Yes", "No"]
          },
          {
            question: "My self-confidence ranges from GREAT self-doubt to EQUALLY GREAT overconfidence.",
            answers: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Very Often"]
          }
    ],
  }